trustmymechanic.com 2011-01-09

# Privacy Statement

**TrustMyMechanic Privacy Statement**

Your privacy is important to us.

     We respect your privacy and will not use any information we obtain from you or about you in any way other than for the purpose specified. We do not sell, rent, loan, or otherwise share email addresses or other personal information that we may collect from you.

     We may occasionally offer online polls, surveys, games, quizzes, or questionaires that require that you provide some personal information, but never in such a way that you can be identified. No names, street addresses, email addresses, or telephone numbers will be requested from you for these purposes.

     For those ordering our What Your Mechanic Doesn't Want You to Know eBook, we use an outside order processing company that collects only appropriate information about you, including credit card information, to complete your order. This company provides a certified secure connection to their processing systems to protect your personal information and privacy. The information collected is used only for processing your order. It is not used in any other way.

     Our order processing company sends us emails containing confirmation of orders, including your name, address, and email address. However, these emails do not contain your credit card information. We save the provided information only for possible future order verification and use the data in no other way.

     Please be aware that Trustmymechanic.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites to which we provide links or with which we have business relationships with. 

If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, you can contact us at **(replace AT with @) austin AT trustmymechanic.com**
